<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DBMS</string>
    <string name="activity1">Introduction</string>
    <string name="definition">"<p align="justify"><b>Database Systems</b> are computer based record keeping system whose overall purpose is to record and maintain information that is relevant to the organization, necessary for making decision. </p>\n"  "<p> Various applications of Real world where database systems are used. \n</p>"<p>1. Banking System and ATM Machines\n2. Stock Trading Systems\n3. Computerized Library Systems\n4. Flight Reservation Systems\n</p>"</string>
    <string name="activity2">"Database System Architecture"</string>
    <string name="abstraction">"<p> In three level architecture of database system, to ease the user interaction with database, the developers hide internal irrelevant details from users. This process of hiding irrelevant details from user is called data abstraction. Layers of database system are <b> View Level </b>, <b>Logical Level </b> and <b> Physical Level </b>. </p> \n"<p>1. View Level: Highest level of data abstraction. It describes the user interaction with database system using GUI. \n</p>""<p>2. Logical Level: This is the middle level of 3-level data abstraction architecture. It describes what data is stored in database in the form of attributes and fields. \n</p>""<p>3. Physical Level: This is the lowest level of data abstraction. It describes how data is actually stored in database. We get the complex data structure details at this level.</p>"</string>
    <string name="activity3">SQL</string>
    <string name="sqlinfo">"<p> Structured Query Language (SQL) is the language used to manipulate relational databases. It is simple and powerful language used to create manipulate and retrieve data and structures in the database. SQL statements are broadly categorized as follows: \n </p>""<p><b>1. Data Definition Language (DDL) Statements:</b> It consists of those statements in SQL languages that are responsible for creating, modifying or dropping database objects such as tables, views etc. For example: CREATE TABLE, ALTER TABLE, DROP TABLE, TRUNCATE, RENAME. \n </p>""<p><b>2. Data Manipulation Language (DML) Statements:</b> SQL commands that deals with the manipulation of data present in the database belong to DML or Data Manipulation Language and this includes most of the SQL statements.\n </p>""<p><b>INSERT</b> – is used to insert data into a table.\n</p>""<p> UPDATE – is used to update existing data within a table.\n </p>""<p> DELETE – is used to delete records from a database table.\n</p>"" <p>3. Data Control Language (DCL) : DCL includes commands such as GRANT and REVOKE which mainly deals with the rights, permissions and other controls of the database system. Examples of DCL commands: GRANT-gives user’s access privileges to database. REVOKE-withdraw user’s access privileges given by using the GRANT command.</p></string>

</resources>
